{
	"title": "toki pona",
	"cards": [
		{
			"question": "a",
			"answer": "any interjection, used to emphasize a word for emotion"
		},
		{
			"question": "akesi",
			"answer": "reptile, amphibian, scaly and/or crawling creature"
		},
		{
			"question": "ala",
			"answer": "No, not, nothing, or simply negation in general. Used to form yes/no questions"
		},
		{
			"question": "alasa",
			"answer": "hunt, search, or forage. Try to do something"
		},
		{
			"question": "ale",
			"answer": "all, entirety, everything. When used as a number, 100"
		},
		{
			"question": "anpa",
			"answer": "bottom, underside, below. lowly, humble, defeat"
		},
		{
			"question": "ante",
			"answer": "other, altered, modified, changed, difference"
		},
		{
			"question": "anu",
			"answer": "a participle to seperate multiple possibilities, replacing another participle. Or just the word 'or'."
		},
		{
			"question": "awen",
			"answer": "stay, remain, pause, protect, keep safe, continue, (when used as a preverb) continue to..."
		},
		{
			"question": "e",
			"answer": "particle that marks the start of a direct object"
		},
		{
			"question": "en",
			"answer": "participle that seperates multiple subjects"
		},
		{
			"question": "esun",
			"answer": "trade, barter, echange, shop, buy. bazaar, fair, place of business, mall"
		},
		{
			"question": "ijo",
			"answer": "thing, object, matter, phenomonan"
		},
		{
			"question": "ike",
			"answer": "bad quality, such as: evil, malice, harmful, bad, unpleasant, complicated"
		},
		{
			"question": "ilo",
			"answer": "tool, implement, machine, device, doohicky, gadget"
		},
		{
			"question": "insa",
			"answer": "inside, center, middle, internal, midpoint, between"
		},
		{
			"question": "jaki",
			"answer": "disgusting, unsanitary, toxic, repulsive, rotten"
		},
		{
			"question": "jan",
			"answer": "human, person, somebody"
		},
		{
			"question": "jelo",
			"answer": "yellow, amber, golden, basically anything between green-yellow and yellow-orange"
		},
		{
			"question": "jo",
			"answer": "hold, carry, possess, contain"
		},
		{
			"question": "kala",
			"answer": "fish, swimming creature, marine animal, sea crature"
		},
		{
			"question": "kalama",
			"answer": "to produce sound, e.g. thunder, drum, laugh, sing, play an instrument, literally anything that has to do with making noise"
		}
	]
}
